var questions = [{
	"question": "What does HTML stands for",
	"opt1": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
	"opt2": "Hyper Text Making Language",
	"opt3": "Hyper Title Markup Language",
	"opt4": "High Text Markup Language",
	"answer": '1'
},
{
	"question": "What does CSS stands for",
	"opt1": "cascading slow sheet",
	"opt2": "cascading shine sheet",
	"opt3": "cascading share sheet",
	"opt4": "cascading style sheet",
	"answer": '4'
},
{
	"question": "function has  ______________ ",
	"opt1": "round braces",
	"opt2": "computer hardware",
	"opt3": "component",
	"opt4": "libraries",
	"answer": '1'
},
{
	"question": "What var stands for in javascript",
	"opt1": "variety",
	"opt2": "varchar",
	"opt3": "vary",
	"opt4": "variable",
	"answer": '4'
},
{
	"question": "extension of javascript is",
	"opt1": ".html",
	"opt2": "js",
	"opt3": "javascript",
	"opt4": ".js",
	"answer": '4'
},
{
	"question": "javascript is a _________________ ",
	"opt1": "scripting language",
	"opt2": "not a functional language",
	"opt3": "prime property language",
	"opt4": "processed language",
	"answer": '1'
},
{
	"question": "What does rgb stands for in HTML",
	"opt1": "red green blue",
	"opt2": "road grass bus",
	"opt3": "rain gun brain",
	"opt4": "High Text Markup Language",
	"answer": '1'
},
{
	"question": "What are objects",
	"opt1": "block of codes",
	"opt2": "internet download function",
	"opt3": "codes with properties ",
	"opt4": "cascading style sheet",
	"answer": '4'
},
{
	"question3": "javascriptfunction has  ______________ ",
	"opt1": "paraments",
	"opt2": "computer hardware",
	"opt3": "console",
	"opt4": "lan card",
	"answer": '1'
},
{
	"question": "What is a use of var in javascript",
	"opt1": "vinitialize",
	"opt2": "create objects",
	"opt3": "vary codes",
	"opt4": "variable datatype",
	"answer1": '1'
},
{
	"question": "extension of javascript is .js name of javascript file preferable is",
	"opt1": "stylel",
	"opt2": "css",
	"opt3": "xml",
	"opt4": "app",
	"answer2": '4'
},
{
	"question": "javascript is a _________________ ",
	"opt1": "library",
	"opt2": "lonely function",
	"opt3": "top quality franchise",
	"opt4": "one of top programming languges",
	"answer": '4'
}

];